backtweets.com 2011-06-23

# Privacy Policy — BackTweets

At BackTweets, we recognize that your privacy is important. We value your trust and confidence and are firmly committed to protecting the privacy of our clients and visitors to our website. BackTweets is not in the business of selling or renting individuals’ personal data to other companies for marketing purposes.

The following documents describe the privacy practices of BackTweets. Below you can find detailed information on when and why we collect personal information, how we use it and the limited conditions under which we may disclose it to others.

BackTweets encourages its users to abide by all applicable laws, rules and regulations, as we promise our clients that we will do ourselves. It is BackTweets’s policy to use cookies (a small text file BackTweets stores locally on your computer for record-keeping purposes) so that you may login to BackTweets without entering your login information. The cookie information does not include personal data such as name, age, phone number, e-mail address or mailing address nor does BackTweets link cookies to personal data such as name, age, phone number, e-mail address or mailing address. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, however, you may set your web browser to reject cookies. For more information on how to reject cookies, see your browser’s instructions on changing your privacy settings.

If you have any questions or comments about this policy, our services, or your experience with BackTweets, please contact us at support+backtweets@backtype.com.
